[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
There was passion...
[Carmen] Can you guys not be freaky
while I'm peeing?
[narrator] ...reconciliation...
I'm sorry on my part.
-Yeah.
-I just want us to be on better terms.
We're making out. we're kissing.
And who walks by?
I've never had a timing situation.
Like. that was real bad.
Leo.
[narrator] ...and three hot bombshells...
-Hi. bitches!
-What's up?
[narrator] ...threw the villa into a spin.
"Smooch the Islander you wanna be
coupled up with." Bergie.
[Bergie] Let's go!
Damn!
"Kiss the Islander
that gives you the ick."
You definitely caught my eye.
Marco. I love him.
I'm sure she could be a cool girl.
but she seems like she don't give a fuck.
[narrator] Tonight...
Right before you walked up.
they were making out.
[narrator] ...emotions...
Had you been making out with Leo?
He kissed me yesterday.
Just to hear that.
it's another jab to the heart.
What the fuck?
[narrator] ...run...
You are the person that I would go for.
If she shows interest in me.
I would give her a chance
to get to know me.
[narrator] ...high.
[Anna] He's a piece of shit.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
Bombshells Emily. Kenzo. and Jonah
are in the villa.
I asked rancher. Jonah.
"What girls do you like?
Do you mind giving me a bit of a steer?"
He handed me a fillet steak.
[cheering]
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Oh. shit.
-Do y'all know how to...
-[Marco] Iron?
...iron?
-[Hannah] Skirt in a middy...
-With a boost.
...with a boost!
Yeah!
S-H-I-E-T.
"Shiet!"
Who all did you talk to so far?
Uh. literally only Marco.
He's really nice.
I like how respectful he seems.
Do you disagree with that?
-I love that she looks deadass at me.
-I was waiting.
[Kenzo] You and Carmen went on a date.
You just weren't feeling that?
-Me and Carmen are really good friends.
-Yeah.
But it was at a point where I was already
in a triangle with Kassy and Anna.
So. Kassy. Anna. and Carmen
in the mix. I'm like. "Bro."
He look real innocent and subtle
and "Fuck me. Daddy."
-See you in a bit.
-All right. awesome.
Your boobs look great.
Thanks.
[Hannah] Now let's get this
show on the road.
[Islander 1] On us.
-What's up. Anna? How you doing?
-Hi.
[chattering]
I'm so excited to be here.
I'm so grateful that everyone's been
so nice and welcoming.
And cheers. bitches.
[all] Cheers!
[Islander 2] We love you.
[narrator] Jonah's a man of many talents.
He looks after 500 head of cattle.
300 chicken.
and he's California's leading Joey
from Friends impersonator.
-How you doing?
-I'm good. I'm just vibing. Obviously.
I'm very single in here.
But where are you at?
What are you looking for in here?
I'm expecting nothing.
but I'm open to everything.
I wanna get to know everyone.
You're all gorgeous. so it's not like...
It really can't come down to looks.
That's what I tell everyone.
-I'm like. "Everyone in here is stunning."
-It can't. It can't.
This is sharks on sharks.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. it's not sharks on minnows. like...
So. I wanna talk to everyone.
I wanna get to know everyone.
I wanna see where everyone's at.
and then start to make decisions of.
you know. "Could it be this?
Could it be that?" And go from there.
Jonah is definitely on my radar.
We definitely share
some similar qualities.
and I think he definitely
radiates good energy.
For me. I understand that I'm okay.
I'm not forgetting that
I'm okay to be independent.
-Yeah.
-If something works out from this. great.
Because I'm so okay
with being independent.
I feel that I would benefit someone
in a relationship now.
Yeah. I'm the same way.
It's like my favorite quality about myself
is how independent I am.
But. like. it'd be really nice
to at least form a connection
and start a relationship with someone.
After my chat with Carmen.
I'm excited to see where things go.
We had a great conversation.
and she seems to wear her heart
on her sleeve.
which I like
because that shows me loyalty.
When she gives her heart to someone.
she really does.
[narrator] Kenzo is chatting to Destiny.
Kenzo offered to give me
some photography lessons.
but to be honest. I struggled to focus.
You're with Harrison now.
How's that going?
Me and Harrison are going good. you know?
I don't have any complaints.
The communication has always been there.
and I told him that I expected him
to get to know people
and. vice versa. that I would...
So. you're still open
to getting to know people?
Absolutely. Yeah.
That's what we're here for. you know?
Yeah. absolutely.
Do you have a specific type
that you look for?
I have to be able
to talk to you intellectually.
You know.
we have to be able to have. like.
spiritual talks or growth talks or...
It does not have to always be serious
about the relationship.
but some way. every single day.
I want us to grow each other.
I think that's really important.
And honestly. that's what life is about.
Is finding people that can help you grow.
Right.
Having a partner like that.
especially with you all the time.
it's something that. like.
it's a necessity. you know?
You think that's why we're here
on this earth. to help each other out.
-I agree.
-You know?
Honestly.
I was very surprised with Destiny.
Like. Destiny really impressed me.
I never expected her to be into
this whole universe and energy thing.
and I'm just very passionate
about these conversations.
And I love how you had the confidence
to walk up to me and pull me for a chat.
Yeah. No.
I really wanted to get to know you. yeah.
-I appreciate that.
-No. you definitely stood out to me.
-Oh. really?
-Yeah.
-I think you're very beautiful. so...
-Oh. thank you.
I wanted to get to know you. and...
-I appreciate that.
-Yeah.
[narrator] Emily's taken a shine
to gold dealer Harrison.
She said. "When we get out here.
will you give me a ring?"
Harrison said. "I'll give you a discount.
but don't push your luck."
-Tell me about yourself.
-So...
I bet you have an interesting story.
-Do you know what? I do.
-I bet you do.
[Harrison] I feel like...
-So. I was born in Australia.
-Okay.
I was obsessed with Australia
when I was younger.
-But where do you even get that kick from?
-I don't even know.
It's just a cool place.
You guys are like the cool.
fun aunts and uncles
that it's like. "They're so cool."
I fucking wish. I wish.
I mean. now. doing the gold
and diamond trading.
-Yeah. you're like. iced out.
-Yeah.
Damn! I didn't even realize the layers.
-Oh. my God.
-Yeah. I enjoy jewelry a lot.
-Yeah.
-What's your story?
What's the deal?
My dad was in the Marines.
-Yeah. moved around a bit.
-Yeah. so I'm in Houston right now
because that's where my family is.
Me and my family are so close.
I see them all the time.
If I don't see them at least
six times a week. I freak out.
-Oh. shit. Really?
-I'm obsessed with my sisters and my mom.
-They're literally my best friends.
-Same with me.
I talk with them like most people
would talk to their best friend.
-Yeah.
-Right? And the trust is always there.
-Your family's not...
-They're not gonna do you dirty.
They're not going anywhere.
They're not gonna do anything like that.
I just love hearing about people's
families 'cause I'm so nosy.
but also. that's why you are
the way that you are.
-You know what I mean? It's so fun.
-Yeah. Definitely.
Obviously you've got such
a close relationship with your family.
-Yeah. They're number one.
-So it's like well...
Yeah. so you wanna kind of see that too
in other people that you hang out with.
Emily's. let's say. caught my eye.
Um... There's interest there.
The conversation flowed really well.
you know.
A bit of bubbliness. which is awesome.
She's... Yeah. she's attractive...
We seem to hit it off a little.
which is good.
[narrator] Kay Kay's sitting with Keenan.
and she's about to ask a question
that has literally no correct answer.
-Are you attracted to her?
-Like...
Physically.
[Keenan] She got some assets.
She got a nice ass. She do.
-She do. Goddamn. She do. Goddamn.
-She do. She do.
-[Kay Kay] She's pretty. too.
-[Keenan] No. for sure.
-I will give her that.
-She ain't me but.
Exactly.
[Kay Kay] But you're willing
to allow her the chance?
[Keenan]
I don't feel like it's fair because. like.
even when I first saw her.
I wasn't attracted to her at all at first.
And then I see her. I said. "Hi." yeah.
all right. You know what I'm saying?
But nothing that I'm actively
looking forward to.
if you know what I'm saying?
-Okay.
-And I would tell you if I was like...
-I believe you.
-No. you should.
-I don't lie to you.
-I know.
Honestly. every time Keenan
tells me something
that should make me feel some type of way.
it makes me like him more
because he's just so honest
and blunt and up-front with me.
She's a pretty girl.
she's got a nice body.
Keenan's into that kind of stuff.
but I'm not too worried about it.
-Yeah.
-You really are my other half.
-I ain't lying. For real. I'm just...
-Aw.
[sighs] Fuck. girl.
[narrator] Destiny wants to know
if Detective Anna holds a grudge.
Anna could hold a grudge.
but if she doesn't charge it
after 24 hours.
the grudge is free to go.
[Destiny] Have you talked to Leo at all?
Only in a group setting.
Everything's okay.
I don't hold grudges. I move on.
and I feel like I won't be able to move on
unless I forgive the situation.
-You deserve the best. honestly.
-Thank you.
Because do you... You don't even know.
When you went to pull him yesterday.
they had just got done making out.
-Kassy and...
-Yeah.
[Anna] Wait. when did this happen?
Right before you walked up.
they were making out
when you went to pull him and call him
on the disrespect for the first time ever.
[Anna] They should've...
They should've waited.
I mean. we're in a couple. babe.
You owe me that respect.
I just would have thought
it would have been relayed.
I just hope I don't look like an idiot
with no self-respect. you know?
Girl. how could you?
You broke up with him immediately.
That's true.
I mean. there is no way you could...
You could look like an idiot
with no self-respect?
No. I think that's
the wrong person to pinpoint.
Actually. no. not that I think. I know
that's the wrong person to pinpoint.
I'm so embarrassed.
Why would you be embarrassed?
I don't know. It's just. like.
I forgive someone. they don't...
Like. it's too soon
for a make-out session.
It's so hurtful that I had forgiven her
and become really close with her today.
and she had all the opportunities
to tell me about it.
I feel like an idiot.
Um. it's very embarrassing.
I feel so disrespected.
It just keeps on coming.
and I'm so over it.
-Is it okay if I steal Kassy for a minute?
-Yeah. go ahead.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Kassy's been kissing Leonardo
behind Anna's back.
and nothing upsets a detective more
than people misbehaving
behind their backs.
It really hurts their...
felons?
-Is it okay if I steal Kassy for a minute?
-Yeah. Go ahead.
-[Kassy] Okay. move.
-[Anna] You move.
-[Leonardo] Yes.
-[Anna] Thank you.
-[Leonardo] I'm gonna just go too.
-Thank you.
-Hello.
Okay.
So I'm gonna ask you something.
I know it's a tough question
to probably answer.
but had you been making out with Leo?
Before that?
He kissed me yesterday.
Before you pulled him for a chat.
That's when he kissed me.
I feel like that's something
that you should have told me.
I didn't tell anybody
except for one person.
Well. he has apparently
been telling people.
-But that doesn't matter. That doesn't...
-What the fuck?
I didn't wanna tell anybody.
It was just between me and him.
And that was literally yesterday.
But that's before I gave you my blessing.
and now I feel like an idiot
for giving you a blessing
when you should have said. like.
this happened.
I... I...
So. it's bad that I got a kiss?
No. it's not bad that you got a kiss.
it's bad that you didn't tell me
when I have been opening up to you.
and I feel like we really reconnected.
and I had forgived you...
-...and we had become...
-So...
-...the kiss...
-...closer than ever today.
And you didn't tell me.
I didn't know he even told people.
I mean. I'm pissed. too.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I thought that was just between
me and him.
I almost feel. like. dumb
for getting super close with you today.
and then just to hear that.
it's another jab to the heart.
I'm a girls' girl.
I am gonna be honest with someone.
especially since they're...
I'm a girls' girl. too.
I don't want you to say that I'm not
because I am. too.
But I didn't know
he was gonna give me that kiss.
if I'm being deadass.
I didn't know. I didn't expect it.
-So you're saying...
-At the same time.
I was happy that he gave it to me.
and I'm sorry that the kiss affected
everything we had.
-I didn't think...
-I just feel like...
-I didn't even know he was gonna do that.
-It's like how...
I'm pissed. too. I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry that you had to find out
through other people.
I know. but I'm saying.
at the end of the day. it sucks
because I wanna see
their relationship grow.
I wanna see it blossom.
and then I hear that...
But that shows me. too.
that he was being immature
by talking to everybody about it.
I don't think you should
blame this on him.
-Okay. Yeah.
-I think that...
-It's both of us. yeah.
-I'm just...
I'm not confronting him 'cause to
be honest. I don't care about him.
-I care about you.
-Yeah. I know.
Yeah. yours is. too.
I care about you so much. dude.
And I'm glad that we had a conversation.
and I'm sorry that you found out
through other people.
And now. whatever that kiss
could have been.
an intimate moment. whatever. it wasn't.
Because I knew in that moment it was bad.
and I didn't wanna do
any more kisses since then.
[Anna] Yeah. I know. I don't have trust
for Kassy right now.
She was more concerned of the fact
of how I found out
rather than what she did.
I'm over it.
I don't wanna continue our friendship
for right now.
and I feel like she should owe people
more respect
instead of humiliating them.
-I just need time.
-Yeah.
-I really just need time.
-Yeah. I'm sorry.
Yeah. yeah. I'm sorry.
Oh. my gosh.
I thought I squashed my drama.
but then somebody.
I have no fucking clue who.
decided to stir a pot that was already...
washed and put away.
[Leonardo] Are you okay?
[Kassy] No. dude.
Where do you wanna go talk?
-Can you talk really quick?
-Yeah. Come with me.
[Kassy] Oh. my gosh.
[Keenan] Well. well. well.
[narrator] Leonardo stirred things up
by telling Destiny he kissed Kassy.
Sometimes it's better to say nothing.
at least according to American TV critics
who've been listening to my voice-over
for the past two weeks.
I didn't see the conversation.
I thought you guys were just...
[Kassy] Like. okay.
Our kiss yesterday.
it was nice and stuff.
Like. I liked our first kiss.
But I obviously wanted that
to be between us two.
-Oh...
-And Anna feels like
I just walked all over her
because we kissed yesterday
and we made up today.
-and she's mad.
-Oh. no.
You know who saw the kiss?
Who?
[whispering] Why are other people
trying to be involved in this?
I don't get why it should be their issue.
If you and I wanna pursue each other.
I don't get what's wrong.
I'm just pissed that somebody is trying
to stir up a pot that was already...
For no reason.
...that was already resolved.
I'm trying to be fucking calm and stuff.
but it's just so annoying
when people try to put themselves in my...
-Into other people's situation. like...
-...problem. dude.
Literally.
stay the fuck out of my situation.
[narrator] As the Islanders head to bed.
Kassy still can't believe that her smooch
with Leonardo had tongues wagging.
That's just Leonardo's kissing technique.
He's very European.
[Destiny] I hate that Anna didn't know.
And I hate that I had to be
the one to tell her.
She deserves to know.
-What's wrong?
-[crying] I just... I hate. like...
Don't cry. Kassy.
It's fucking...
annoying.
Are you gonna build your wall. Anna?
No. he's sleeping outside.
[Hannah] He is?
-[Marco] Yeah.
-[Hannah] Okay.
[Marco] I think he's gonna try
to give you some space tonight.
We patched up our friendship again.
We're good.
I don't think she's mad at me like that.
I just want her to have a bed to herself.
[Kenzo] Yeah.
[Islander] The bug is out here. though.
homey. I ain't gonna lie to you.
So quiet. Wasn't expecting that.
-I was like. "Are you okay?"
-You don't have to sleep outside.
Good night. I hope the mosquitoes
aren't too bad.
Carmen. come here. Real quick.
Would it be bad
if I sleep out here with him?
No. I think you should.
and you should own it.
And I think you guys
should be doing it together.
[Kassy giggling]
What a night.
-[Harrison] Welcome to the party.
-Thank you.
You're gonna need that.
[Kassy] Are you tired?
Yes and no.
I'm just happy
that I'm next to you. honestly.
-I was tired all day.
-Aw...
Oh. shit. look.
That's so sick.
[Kassy] Aw.
-That's actually so fucking cool.
-It looks really nice. actually.
-[Leonardo] Yeah.
-[Kassy] Do you like being big spoon?
[Leonardo] I love being big spoon.
I love being little spoon.
[kisses]
Good morning!
-[Emily] I heard you snoring.
-Oh. shit. Sorry.
And you do this thing where you go "Mmm."
[Keenan] How are you guys?
First night in the villa.
y'all got to sleep
in the Love Island beds.
-Congrats. Welcome. welcome.
-Yay!
[Emily] I was gonna say.
"I'm fully rested."
[Kenzo] You slept pretty good.
Just so much went down yesterday
that I was just so ready for a good sleep.
[both] Good morning.
[Kenzo] Thanks. bro.
I might just have to keep you as my...
[Harrison] He gonna couple up. [laughs]
Good morning.
[Keenan imitating eating sounds]
What's up. Bergie?
This actually seems kind of nice
to sleep out here.
Me and Anna were good.
but for Destiny. yeah.
I thought we were cool for her.
What the fuck?
Why did you even bring that up
knowing that...
-we squashed everything?
-Yeah.
The reason is probably just.
"Oh. I don't want this girl
looking stupid."
So forth and so on.
She can talk to me about it.
[Jonah] You guys are starting early.
[Marco] Heck. yeah. We always do.
If I don't start early.
I'll never get here.
[Keenan] Hey. Jonah Jones.
What's up. baby boy?
[narrator] It's been a tough
24 hours for Kassy.
and the situation
is beginning to get her down.
[Emily] Kassy.
you work out when you're here?
[sighs] I did
a long time ago.
But I feel like
I just never have time anymore.
It sucks.
Kass. are you okay?
Um... [sighs]
Yeah. But you know. a little bit...
I just don't wanna cry. It's just...
This isn't me.
It's just straining.
And I just...
Being like this.
I wanna talk to Anna and apologize
because the kiss didn't come up in my head
when I was talking to her.
And...
Yeah.
And I just...
I feel like I'm a bad person in here.
and I know I'm not.
And it just sucks
because I just...
I don't know. It's a lot to... And look...
I just... I wish...
It's gonna be okay.
Just let it ride out. You know?
I am here for love...
and...
it just sucks that I can't...
For me. it's not...
it hasn't been an easy journey.
[Kay Kay] I think just
give her space for now. and then...
I know.
-...she'll be open to talk.
-I wanna be in a good space. too...
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
-...when I talk to her.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
-[Emily] Hey. Keenan.
-[Keenan] What's up?
[Emily] You wanna to come
have a chitchat with me?
[Keenan] Yeah. I got you. sweetheart.
What do you wanna talk about. sweetheart?
Let's go there
'cause I haven't been over here yet.
[Keenan] All right. bet.
How are you feeling?
[Emily] I'm feeling good.
I'm just trying to. like...
get to know every single person. I guess.
As you should. You owe it to yourself.
I know that you're. like.
pretty comfortable with Kay Kay.
and I wanna respect it. but I also. like...
I don't know. outside of here.
I think you are. like.
the person that I would go for.
You. like. hit all the spots. looks wise.
-You know what I mean?
-Stop.
I'm not even trying to hype you up.
It's just a question and an answer.
[Emily laughing]
What's all that giggling
and "kiki-ing" and "kaka-ing" over there?
Shit. My man.
[laughing]
He is not that fucking funny.
-[Keenan] When's your birthday?
-[Emily] March 30th.
-[Keenan] You Pisces?
-[Emily] I'm Aries.
[Keenan] Aries? Okay.
You're my first Aries ever.
-[Emily] Really?
-[Keenan] Yeah.
-Tell me about Aries a little bit.
-I could be a bitch.
-For real? But that's fine.
-Yeah.
[Keenan] All right. Goddamn.
you speak your mind.
-[Emily] I do. I know what I'm feeling.
-[Keenan] Okay.
So then. what are you feeling?
-About you?
-Yeah.
[Emily] I'm feeling it.
[Keenan] You know.
Emily is an attractive girl.
I'm not going to downplay it.
It was a really well conversation.
A little flirt here and there.
but. um. yeah. it was...
It's very apparent
that the physical attraction is there.
-Yeah!
-...see what I'm saying. I didn't notice...
[Kay Kay]
They're talking over there forever.
I haven't got to talk to my man all day.
-Is he with Emily?
-Yeah.
[Hannah] He's been over there
the whole time.
I wouldn't say I'm threatened.
Never threatened.
I don't know.
I just don't know what to expect.
We are still open.
I know. Yeah.
As much as the bombs
have been trying to bomb.
she seems like the first one
that doesn't give a fuck.
-She's ready to blow shit up.
-Yeah.
[Emily] Him and I had. like.
the most fun conversation that I've had.
Really liked talking to him.
And he shows so much interest in me
when we're talking.
It came really natural.
and we both have
a lot of similar interests.
and. like. he's just really fun.
-Breath of fresh air.
-You get what I'm saying?
-Yeah.
-Just the vibe. No drama.
[Emily] You're not moving weird at all.
-I'mma gonna let you go. girl.
-Bye.
-All right. Bye.
-Nice to get to know you.
For sure.
[narrator] Leonardo's pulled Anna
so he can put this Kassy business to bed.
It was the business
you got up to in bed with Kassy
that caused all the problems
in the first place. mate.
[Leonardo] I just wanted to. like.
just clear out some air.
-Okay. Okay.
-You know. just express where I was at.
But. um...
So for one.
I wanted to apologize
because I know I put you through a lot.
and you definitely didn't deserve that.
The biggest apology is just. like.
how I went about kissing Kassy.
Try to just go about it in my own way.
away from you.
without trying to do things
in front of you.
Which is why I pulled it to the side over
there. away from the group.
I just feel really bad
for disrespecting you. and I know...
Do you. though?
I mean. you did sleep in a bed
with her last night.
Like. do you have a reason for that?
We had a good moment
at the end of the night.
but then right after that. it got worse.
I didn't want you to have to. like.
"Okay. now I have to see this guy again."
Or maybe I went about that wrong.
So. I apologize.
I'm disappointed
because I have people coming to me
telling me that you guys kissed
before we had that conversation.
and you had time to tell me.
Like. how embarrassing is it
to hear that from other people
you guys had kissed
when I had forgiven Kassy.
and I was on my way to forgiving you?
You've shown your true colors
as well as Kassy did.
and that's not people
I want in my life in general.
It just sucks that we're living
in the same house.
It makes me look stupid.
It makes me feel stupid.
I thought we had something
really good growing. so it sucks.
But I need to respect myself.
And that's me saying
I don't wanna talk to you anymore.
[Anna] I don't know how many mistakes
you can make
and just keep apologizing
and not learn from them.
I wasn't interested in the conversation.
I really just wanna move on
and forget about the past.
But I'm not gonna be his friend.
At the end of the day.
you don't treat someone like that.
especially someone that cared
and liked you a lot.
So that's what hurts.
I have too much respect for myself
to continue even talking to you
as a friend right now.
-I understand.
-Thank you.
[Leonardo] Damn.
Do you think I should take
my sideburns off?
[Marco] What? No.
-[Harrison] No.
-[Bergie] No. don't do that.
[narrator] Roll up. Roll up.
It's Keenan the Magnificent.
And he's about to make a lady disappear
using only words.
-[Keenan] It was a good chat or whatever.
-[Kay Kay] Mm-hmm.
[Keenan] It was just like I was saying.
it was definitely a vibe there.
Of course. way better convos
than Kassy. though. I will say that.
But that's not saying too much.
[Kay Kay] To me. that's saying a lot.
[Keenan] If she shows interest.
I will give her a chance
to get to know me.
I have a brain.
I don't think with my dick.
you know what I'm saying?
And there's certain things
that I want and look for.
[Kay Kay] That's fine.
It's just very uncomfortable for me.
You know what? Let me not be the bad kid.
But I'm just saying this
just because of the tension.
You were just in the Hideaway
the other night and...
now he wants to get to know someone else?
Like. I feel like we're too far in this
to still be. like. testing shit out.
He had a test already.
Like. what more do you need to know?
'Cause I don't want y'all another week in.
and now y'all giving each other
fucking googly eyes.
Let me know now.
Keenan likes her.
He just told me he likes her.
-[Hannah] Who did?
-Keenan.
[Anna] I'm sorry. what?
Keenan likes her.
Oh. my God. You had just fucking
had intimate moments with him.
and then he fucking does that?
I was just getting my ear chewed out.
They feel a certain type of way.
And I didn't even do shit.
-About who?
-About the conversation. all that stuff.
It is going to be
a little bit of backlash.
-but it is what it is. bro.
-[Harrison] All right. Whatever.
[Anna] You're a fucking wifey.
I feel like this always
fucking happens to me.
Watch it play out.
If this happens.
that's not the guy you wanna be with.
Like. every single guy
that I finally start to like.
they always pick someone who's more fun.
more bubbly. more anything...
Kay Kay. you are that fucking bitch.
[Keenan] I mean. I'm good. I'm fine.
I feel like I haven't done...
No. I haven't done shit wrong. bro.
-That's right. That's right.
-I haven't done shit wrong.
-No doghouse for him.
-You know what I'm saying?
You're not boring. You're not boring.
[Anna] He's a piece of shit
if he's gonna say that.
He's a piece of fucking shit.
You're too fucking good for him.
That's what it is.
He's a piece of shit for letting you
have intimate time
and then still being open.
Just feel like nothing's good enough.
You are too good enough.
That's exactly what it is.
He's just being a shitty person right now.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Emily and Bergie are on the swing chair.
By the way. that "Breathe" sign's
just a reminder.
Someone forgot to do it last series.
and we had to send in the paramedics.
-It's so pretty today.
-[Bergie] Yeah.
[Bergie] The ocean. too. and the sun.
I feel like it's perfect.
Where are you from again?
-Minnesota. Minnesota.
-Wisconsin?
-Minnesota?
-Yeah. Minnesenota.
-You say it like that?
-No.
-You guys don't talk like that.
And then... The movie Fargo.
it's like. "What's up. eh?"
-I got my first text!
-[screaming]
Oh. my God! What do I do?
-[Anna] I'm screaming.
-[Kenzo] There's a text.
[Anna] I'm screaming!
-[Hannah] Get ready.
-Fuck.
[Keenan] Who got the text?
[Emily] I got a text.
[Islander] Hey. now.
"Emily. Kenzo. and Jonah.
today you will each choose two Islanders
you want to go on dates with."
They get two dates?
"Please make your decision now
and get ready for your first date.
#AWhiskWorthTaking
and #I'mYourBiggestFlan."
[Harrison] Well. shit.
-Kenzo. go first.
-[Kenzo] All right.
So. the girl I would like
to take on a date is um...
Carmen.
[Leonardo] Big Kenzo.
[Jonah] I would like to go on a date with...
Hannah.
The boy I wanna take on a date is...
Marco.
[Emily] My first date. I picked Marco.
This is like the perfect way for him
to know how interested I am.
Putting an action to what I'm saying.
you know what I mean?
'Cause I want him to know. like.
"You're up there."
Here we go.
[narrator] The bombshells'
dates are on their way.
Emily picked Marco. Kenzo picked Carmen.
and Jonah picked Hannah.
And for this one.
the date team have gone all out.
Hang on. I read that wrong.
The date team have all gone out.
So. our lot are gonna be stuck
in the garden eating cold quiche.
[Hannah] I see bubbly.
We got that bubbly. Hey.
-[Kenzo] What's up?
-[Carmen] Hi.
-[Carmen] You look so cute.
-[Kenzo] You look really good. too.
Thank you.
[Jonah] How are you? You look pretty.
-Hello. You look great.
-Hi.
[Hannah] Thank you. You. too.
-[Emily] Well. thank you.
-[Marco] Yeah. no problem.
[Carmen] This is cute.
I wasn't expecting this.
-[Kenzo] I know.
-Let me pull this out.
-[Hannah] Thank you so much.
-[Jonah] Backtrack.
-Hold on.
-Gentleman.
-Thank you.
Of course.
I like your outfit a lot.
-I love the brown.
-Really?
That little chain you got.
You know what I mean?
-Should we do a little cheers? Okay.
-Yeah. a little cheers.
What are we "cheers-ing" to?
To a beautiful experience
and to hopefully finding love.
-I love it. There we go.
-Salud. Salud.
Salud.
[Anna] I'm wearing
sunglasses for a reason.
Stalker mode is activated.
So. your dad lives in Scottsdale as well?
-Mm-mmm.
-Or he's in Wisconsin?
Both my parents are in Wisconsin.
They've been together since my mom was 18
and my dad was 20.
and they got married very young.
-Yeah.
-But they're. like.
to this day.
still obsessed with each other.
-They love each other so much.
-That's awesome.
And as much as I love them for it.
I'm like.
"Y'all really raised the bar for me."
I'm like. "Why would I settle
for anything less?"
Like. I'm just so used to seeing
such healthy love. you know?
And you're really nice.
and you're beautiful.
and you honestly deserve the best.
-So you definitely shouldn't settle.
-Thanks.
[Keenan] I know that boy. Kenzo.
is cooking in that damn sun.
I know. bro.
We should throw him the lamp
with the shades.
Literally. It's directly in his face.
He said. "Uh-huh. Yeah."
I don't go to the clubs anymore.
I like places that. like.
yeah. like bars. where you can
-actually talk to someone.
-Yeah.
Even. like.
go and do an adventure.
go camping or something like that
for a weekend.
You have to open my eyes up to that.
I don't think I've ever
gone camping in my life.
-You can take me when we get back.
-Yeah. I'll take you.
I won't be mad about that.
[Kenzo] When I came in.
Carmen was the first one
that caught my eye right away.
And so I think that chemistry right there
that just started.
it's almost set a fire.
and it just hasn't gone away.
What do you like do for fun?
Camping. Hiking.
-You like to camp?
-I love to camp.
-I like to camp.
-I fly-fish.
-You and my dad have a lot in common.
-Really?
He wanted to make sure that
we knew how to do stuff for ourselves.
So. we know how to fish.
Once you catch them...
-Skinning it?
-Yes. all that stuff.
-I don't like it. but...
-Okay.
We know how to do it.
You're ready for the zombie apocalypse?
I think I could survive a good minute.
-That's good.
-For sure.
-That's a good quality to have.
-Yeah...
You must be feeling me.
-A little bit.
-Yeah?
-Yay.
-Most of my family is Hispanic.
-Right.
And then. half my family is Black.
I feel like I'm getting to know you and...
-Yeah.
-That's huge for me.
I definitely felt like
we got along really easy.
I don't know if 'cause
we're both from Cali and we both.
like. you said you have a lot of family
from different backgrounds.
-Yeah.
-You remind me of my dad a lot.
-Uh-oh.
-Not in a bad way.
I love my dad.
But the good qualities about him.
for sure.
[Jonah] The conversation
was flowing very fluidly.
Everything we talk about.
we seemed to relate more and more on.
So. I'm definitely excited
to continue to pursue it.
I like to go after what I want.
so when it's time to go get it.
it's time to go get it.
[Bergie] I think she likes Jonah.
but I don't know. I really don't know.
Only time will tell.
Obviously. you know.
-you're a gorgeous girl. Beautiful.
-Thank you.
My type is. you know. tan skin. dark hair.
So. you fit right in the type of mine.
-Cool.
-I was thrown off.
I couldn't believe it. you know?
Oh. so you were looking for me?
-Yeah. I was looking around.
-Oh. shoot.
[Keenan] Wait. can Marco see Hannah?
Yeah. Marco's looking at the back
of Hannah's head.
He's just like. "Uh-huh."
Am I gonna keep making the first moves.
I guess?
-Oh. boy. That is a tough question.
-'Cause this is the thing.
This is the thing.
I do respect you and her.
but at a certain point.
I gotta feel pursued as well.
-Some move back. yeah.
-Yeah.
I'm open to have a reciprocal
type of bond grow here.
And if I feel that I can grow from this.
you will be pursued. you know?
I like a dominant guy.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
I just wanna be like.
"Oh. my God. he's such a man."
So. you like kind of being able
to renovate houses. fix sinks.
Yeah. Like. if I want you
to build me a table.
Yeah. no problem.
I want to come home on Sunday morning
and be like.
"Oh. my God. It's exactly what I wanted."
-"Table's built."
-Yeah. "Table's built."
My date with Marco.
we have an instant connection.
If we maybe put a little bit more effort.
it could be really good.
-I had so much fun.
-Yeah. I know. Me. too.
I feel like every time we talk.
I feel like it just gets better
and better.
Agreed. Who are you feeling
for your next date
so I can go get them for you?
Can you go grab me Anna. please?
-[Carmen] Yeah. I got you.
-[Kenzo] Sweet.
-Bye.
-It was great talking to you.
Had a good date. I'll go get Anna for you.
Thank you. I enjoyed talking to you.
I enjoyed talking to you. too.
Okay. Who do you want me to grab?
Now. if you can go grab me...
-Destiny.
-Okay.
-Great date.
-I had so much fun.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you for having a date with me.
-You're welcome.
-I had a really good time.
Will you send Harrison over?
-Harrison? Yeah.
-Please?
[Marco] Okay. Bye. honey.
-I'll give you a hug.
-[Emily] Thank you. Bye.
-Bye.
-It was nice talking.
[Marco] You as well.
[narrator]
It's time for the second round of dates.
A chance for Destiny. Anna. and Harrison
to enjoy scintillating conversation
and a plate of half-eaten quiche.
-[Kenzo] What's up?
-[Anna] Hi.
-[Kenzo] You look so good.
-I couldn't match you.
-I'm sorry.
-You what?
-I tried my best to match.
-It's okay. We look good like this.
Hey. hottie!
-She looks cute as fuck.
-You look sexy.
-Am I supposed to sit right here?
-Yeah. You can go here.
Ah! Thank you.
What is this?
-It looks like French quiche.
-[Kenzo] Pizza?
-I'm so glad you pulled me.
-Are you really?
I haven't been able to talk to you.
-I know. How you doing?
-I'm good. thank you.
[Jonah] Good. Come here.
-Do you have a type or no?
-I go for the bad boys.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Come over here.
Do I look like a bad boy?
No. you don't. I mean. in a way. yeah.
-I change a lot.
-Yeah.
I feel like I can be very quiet
and a huge listener.
-Yeah.
-Or I can be very outgoing and loud.
-Good. I wanna see that more.
-Or I can be very mysterious.
Rawr.
-What do you think my sign is?
-You're like. "Wrong pick."
I don't know anything about...
Are you a Gemini?
I'm a Gemini. So I'm just saying that.
Do you know much about signs?
I know just about my sign a little bit.
-What is it?
-Scorpio.
-When's your birthday?
-October 27th.
Okay.
I'm more into goofy personalities.
clearly. 'cause I'm a fucking weirdo.
And I love that about you.
and that's why I picked you.
'Cause a lot of people
might think you're wild.
but I like that about someone.
especially if that's who you are.
and you're not afraid to show it.
To me. that's very attractive.
Aw. thank you.
Are you gonna start doing this
across the room to me?
"Come here. Let's start breakdancing."
But. yeah. I love how you express yourself
and everything like that.
So should I show my titties more?
Obviously. like. physically.
I'm attracted to you.
Yeah. I'm attracted to you. too. Rawr.
I'm like. "Come over here."
Like. "Just take it off."
The date with Anna
honestly went really good.
She was just being really free
and just making jokes.
And I really liked that.
So. honestly. I'm starting
to like her a lot more.
I'm surprised we have not gotten
to talk at all.
That's why I pulled you.
Look at you.
-Psychology.
-Stir up the pot.
Stir up the...
-And you stirred it. you know?
-Hey. hey.
Hey.
[laughing]
-Damn. I could hear Jonah.
-I can hear Jonah from here.
-[Keenan] What's up with Destiny?
-[Carmen] They're animated now.
Destiny and Jonah
are going back and forth.
Destiny's... A lot more movement.
even from the behind.
[Keenan] Yeah. Her shoulders are like...
Her hair's swaying. She's talking like
this. and he's giggling.
So tell me about the type of woman
you normally go for.
I go for a personality.
I like someone that's really extroverted.
-Mm-hmm.
-Someone that can roll with the punches.
Quote. unquote. "like to be
the center of attention."
And I like smart.
Now. what is it you say you do?
Well.
I'm checking every box you done named.
-I'm a microbiologist.
-Okay.
So I studied science.
I have a bachelor's degree.
and I also have a master's degree.
Hell. yeah.
-A little brainiac.
-Good job.
-You know. a little smart.
-I like that.
-Thank you.
Jonah's a nice man.
He's bubbly. he's extroverted.
I didn't find myself
looking at Harrison at all.
I was definitely focused
on the person in front of me.
Would you describe yourself more as calm...
kind of pretty collected?
I think I'm easygoing.
but I don't think I'm calm.
I'm a pretty serious guy. I have to admit.
Yeah. you seem...
-Do I?
-You kind of do.
-Yeah.
I feel like I'm always the energetic one.
-Good to have energy. right?
-Yeah.
Maybe it's good that
you're more on the serious side
because I'm a lot.
I mean. they do say
positive and negatives attract. right?
Yeah. because we can't both be crazy.
-Yeah.
-You can't be on my level all the time.
That would just be annoying.
I think we're doing pretty good.
-[Harrison] I would agree. I would agree.
-Yeah.
I like the way things are going.
Would you say you do. too?
Yeah. I feel like I just did.
Well. I wanted to hear you say it again.
-Okay. I like the way things are going.
-[giggles] Yay.
-Cheers to that.
-Cheers.
[Harrison] So far. so good.
There's a lot of eye contact there
which is great.
She's caught my eye
and piqued my interest.
So. yeah. All right.
-So. we're playing footsies already?
-Yeah.
-Keeping it to yourself.
-Look out. Yeah.
-We'll save that for later.
-Yeah.
Uh-oh. uh-oh. He's getting engaged.
He's talking about diamonds or jewels.
He's gotta be.
[Kay Kay] She must've
complimented his earrings.
She's like. "Those are really nice."
He's talking about the value of gold
increasing last week.
Okay.
How are you and Harrison?
Yeah. I'm glad you asked that.
Me and Harrison have an understanding
that we're open.
He is the newest addition here.
He's not the newest edition. baby.
I know. That's right.
[laughing]
I love how you checked that. I like that.
I like a man that can. you know.
show some badness.
I can tell you got spice.
I can answer your spice with spice.
You can handle this spice?
-I can handle the spice.
-You like spice?
I like Tabasco and Tapatio. Put it on me.
[laughing]
You guys leaning over.
-I think their date's going well.
-It is going well.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
After their dates with Jonah and Emily.
Destiny and Harrison are comparing notes
while gazing at a picture of me
that I pinned to a nearby palm tree.
-That's beautiful. Jesus.
-It is.
[Destiny] Okay. so. Jonah.
he's a nice man.
you know. for sure.
Very nice.
-[Harrison] Yeah.
-[Destiny] Very kind. you know.
What about yours? How'd yours go?
The conversation flowed
really. really naturally.
And so. that was nice.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
So far. I like what I see. you know?
-Okay. so you're interested.
-She's nice.
-So. you're interested?
-I would say so.
I'm not gonna
beat around the bush and lie.
I don't expect you to.
That's why we having this conversation.
-Exactly. Exactly.
-Okay.
So. would you say it's worth...
breaking our couple for?
I'm not gonna say that.
Not at all. It's been. what. two hours?
The minute I do think that...
-Mm-hmm.
-...I'll let you know.
I feel like. again.
communication is part of our base.
This is an interesting situation.
Yes. we know Mr. Harrison
is a hot commodity. but so am I.
So. Jonah chose me out of everyone
he could have chose for a date.
You know. it's just nice
to even your playing field a bit
or show your potential as well.
So. how was everyone's dates today?
My first date was with Marco.
and it went really. really. really well.
I feel like at this opportunity.
she knows I'm comfortable where I'm at.
If she's gonna come in.
she better come with energy.
she better come to get me.
And then my second date was with Harrison.
and that one was definitely
more. like. lighthearted.
And there was a lot more banter and fun.
I'm definitely interested
in getting to know Harrison a lot more.
Destiny. you went on a date. too.
with Jonah.
I did have a date.
He said he likes some spice.
So. I said okay.
'cause I come with a whole cayenne pepper.
boo. like. hot tamale on me.
What about you. Carmen?
I had a good time.
I felt a connection
as soon as I came in the house.
-We locked eyes and...
-I peeped. I peeped.
[laughing]
But I know he's still keeping his cards
a little bit close to his chest.
so it's like no one really knows
where the new boys are at.
Anna. you went on a date with him. too?
How was your date with him?
I feel like he opened up a little bit.
Obviously. I want to talk to him more.
It was great. It was so much fun.
[cheering]
This game is fucking amazing.
No. not sideways.
This is not no goofy goober. bro.
Come on now.
[Marco] Come on. help my boy out.
You can see my panty.
No idea what's on the agenda tonight.
[Jonah] All right.
Cheers to making great connections.
to being around beautiful people.
and to having a great fucking time.
-Yeah!
-Cheers!
[chattering]
-[Emily] Oh. Keenan.
-[Keenan] We gotta talk.
[Emily] Would you like to
have a chitchat with me. please?
[Kay Kay] Not right now.
-[Keenan] We can't talk right now?
-[Kay Kay] No.
[Keenan] Why? What's up?
[Kay Kay] I don't give a damn.
[Keenan] I'm gonna go ahead
and just chat. all right?
-I'll be back.
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
-[Emily] Where do you wanna go?
-[Keenan] Away.
[Kay Kay] Yeah. sure.
-[Keenan] You good. You look sexy.
-[Emily] Sexy?
[Keenan] No. you look nice. though.
[Leonardo] How are we all feeling?
-How are you feeling?
-[Kay Kay] Not great.
-[Leonardo] For real? Why?
-[Kay Kay] Yeah. I don't know.
[Leonardo] Are you worried?
[Kay Kay] I think he likes her.
He'll be like.
"Yeah. the conversation was good.
I liked our chat.
I am open to getting to know her."
But it kind of left me like. "Fuck."
-[Kassy] Yeah.
-Yeah.
-Where do you wanna sit at?
-Over here's good.
All right. How are you?
I'm good.
For real? What you got on your mind?
I'm just kind of narrowing down
who's making it for me and who's not.
And...
I think what I am looking for
is someone who's fun to talk to.
who. like. makes me feel like.
"That was a fun conversation."
You know?
And I definitely had that
with you the other day.
Oh. for real?
You were my favorite conversation I think...
-I appreciate that. Stop it.
-...I've had.
I think you need to know by now.
I'm not trying to flatter you none.
Please. You'd have been flattering me
since we walked over here.
Got down on me. making me blush.
I wanted to talk to Keenan because he was
my favorite conversation I've had.
I think he and I
naturally had such a good flow.
And also. he's one of the people
I'm the most attracted to in here as well.
Like. he's my type.
Why didn't you choose me for a date. then?
-You had two.
-Because...
-I didn't even make the count on two.
-Can I be honest?
Because I was gonna...
You were. like. heavily on my mind.
I'm willing to stir the pot.
and I'm gonna do it.
And I'm gonna piss some people off.
Knowing that you and Kay Kay
were in the Hideaway.
that plays a part in my
decision-making process. for sure.
I feel like I really
never get that opportunity
to test other connections.
And I'm gonna be honest.
that's very important for me.
The Hideaway didn't really help either.
It's not that I'm looking to have
this "Love Island experience" or whatever.
it's more so.
I want to test our connection
and just make sure it's the strongest
'cause the whole point of being here
is finding your best romantic connection.
Yet I've only been able to make one.
Obviously. we vibe.
And I've made it known that we vibe.
I didn't keep that a secret
'cause I told Kay Kay from the jump.
like. if I'm attracted.
if we vibe. I'll let you know.
And I let her know.
The conversation was great.
the vibe was there.
But that date was your leverage
for me to actually open the door.
-Did you think I was gonna pick you?
-Definitely.
-I definitely did.
-You did?
-At least for the second one.
-Really? That kind of shocks me.
Damn. I didn't...
I didn't think you were. like.
thinking like that.
-Well. shoot.
-Yeah.
That kind of changes. like.
my perspective of everything.
-We'll see about that.
-I'm not going nowhere.
-It's like...
-I don't like it.
I really thought that was the moment.
So. when I really get that moment.
I was like. "Shit. goddamn."
-Sorry.
-I'm gonna fall back.
I kind of like that. though.
You're a gorgeous girl.
You ain't going nowhere no time soon.
So. I mean. with respect.
we will see if anything can progress.
Yeah. You want me to put effort.
-And then I can return...
-I get you.
-I get what you're saying. Yeah.
-You got what I'm saying?
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Hair stylist. Emily.
is looking at Keenan thinking.
"Get my scissors. I'd like to snip
a little something off the back."
Kay Kay is looking at Keenan thinking.
"Get my scissors. I'd like to snip
a little something off the front."
I mean penis.
-[Hannah] You don't want to be able to...
-No.
[Hannah] Let me see.
-Yeah. Go to the swing.
-Okay.
Sorry. I'm so complicated.
[Hannah] No. you're fine. I get it.
-I'd be the same way. but worse.
-[Kay Kay] Yeah.
I don't want him to feel like
he is being watched.
Okay.
I need my Hannah time because I feel like...
of everyone. you're the most levelheaded.
and I feel like you get me.
Thank you.
But. like. we're levelheaded.
We're realistic. but still. it's like...
-Fuck.
-Fuck. Exactly.
Definitely.
So. have you been able to talk to him?
-No.
-Right.
As soon as we had a moment.
Emily came and pulled him for a chat.
-and I told her "no."
-Good.
[Kay Kay] And Keenan was like.
"Let me go have this chat really quick."
Okay. real quick. that's a good answer.
All right. whatever.
It's not like that I didn't want him
to talk to her.
No. You wanted a little time.
Yeah. but I just don't like it
when you steal time from me.
-Exactly. It is.
-That's my time.
The fact that we went to the Hideaway
and had that experience.
and then the day we come out.
you're wanting to get to know someone.
just makes me feel so fucking stupid.
Of course. we both have the agreeance
that we're not closed off.
-Yeah.
-But. like.
why am I not enough for you?
You've gotten everything from me.
And that's what makes me feel stupid.
I shouldn't have done that.
No. but you can't feel stupid
because you've done all that you feel.
Who has been in here enough
to turn your head?
-No one.
-Exactly.
'Cause Kay Kay. you're the full package.
I'm not even just hyping you
when I say that.
You got your shit together.
You're gorgeous.
-So. you are enough.
-Thank you.
I don't want you to think
you're not enough.
It would make sense if he's like.
"I really got a strong
emotional connection with a girl."
Something like that. But you're talking
about you vibe with her.
Yeah. You like the vibe. so...
You don't let a vibe
come between us. like.
please.
-He's still very much open.
-Yeah.
-And Kay Kay needs to be the same way.
-Right.
Thank you.
So. I'm not saying
cut things off with him.
-Right.
-But it's like.
-all right. "I see how it is."
-Right. Don't be the dumb bitch.
Don't be dumb.
Right now. I'm feeling
very overwhelmed emotionally.
I'm the nicest person.
the most welcoming person.
but me and Keenan look like we're
freaking married around the villa. so...
But that don't be stopping them girls
from chatting with him.
So. the fuck is this?
[phone chimes]
-Oh. my God. I got a text! I got a text!
-[all cheering]
-She got a text!
-Shit.
-Fuck.
-Oh. my God.
-I love you so much.
Thank you for talking to me.
[Hannah] No. of course I always got you.
He's always got you. too.
-[Marco] You know I got you. Kay Kay.
-Thank you.
[Emily] Okay.
"Tonight there will be a recoupling."
Whoa!
Fuck.
Um. Shit. "Kenzo. Emily. and Jonah.
you will choose first.
#LastInFirstPick.
#ShuffleTheDeck."
[Islander] Yeah! Shit!
Oh. shit.
I've gone for extremely strong
couples thus far.
but I don't really care about
stepping on people's toes so much
that it's gonna. like.
play into who I pick.
I'm just gonna do what I need to do
to get what I want.
Oh. my goodness.
[narrator] Next time...
A recoupling...
The boy I would like to couple up with...
The girl...
I would like to couple up with...
...is...
[narrator] ...causes chaos.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm